ANGELICA TUTOR BUAN



- Flat 27, 2nd floor Haider Bldg 2 Muraggabat, Dubai UAE
- +971545935722
- Angelica.tutor18@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Nursing assistant with vast knowledge of medical terminology and infection control standards. Expertise with developmental factors specific to pediatric, adult and geriatric care facility residents. Analytic and strategic nursing assistant with excellent problem solving and time management skills. Organized, efficient and always willing to go the extra mile to meet expectations.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Problem Solving
- Quality Assurance
- Communication
- Leadership
- Infection Control
- Patient Assessments

- Attention to detail
- Patient Feeding
- Patient Relations
- Supply Restocking
- Empathy
- Mobility Assistance

EDUCATION

Filipino Institute, Dubai, UAE CERTIFIED NURSING ASSISTANT March 2022

Maryhill College, Lucena City, Philippines
BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION
MAJOR IN HUMAN RESOURCE MANAGEMENT
April 2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nursing Assistant, July 2022 - Current Prime Healthcare Group, Dubai, UAE

- Vital signs
- Maintaining the health and well-being of the patients
- Providing physical and emotional support to patients
- Preparing them for physical examinations, laboratory tests and medical visits

Admin Officer, Nov. 2018 – May 2022 **Mk Group**, Dubai, UAE

- Responsible for providing administrative support to the organization
- Organizing company's records, overseeing company's budget and inventory of stocks
- Create and modify employee schedules

HR Assistant, June 2014 – July 2018 **Sanford Marketing Corp.**, Lucena City, Philippines

- Ensures that the organization employs the right balance of staff in terms of skills and experience
- Training and development
- Implement policies

TRAININGS

- Basic Life Support (G2015)
- Basic Pluc CPR and AED

ANGELICA T. BUAN

I hereby certify that the above information is true and correct.